A Guide to the Rockefeller Unviersity records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Reports FA983
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Unviersity records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Reports
1926-1979
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University.
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA983
0.88 Cubic Feet 2 document boxes
2 document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 130.5-U
Arrangement
Chronological
Scope and Contents
A selection of reports, proposals and reviews.
- A Report on the Developments of the First Twenty Years of the Rockefeller Institute and an Outlook for Future Growth. Presented at the meeting of the Board of Scientific Directors, 1926 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Report to the Members of the Corporation Covering a Review of the First Twenty Five Years of the Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1930 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Scientific Report to the Members of the Corporation, 1950-1951, 1951 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Proposal to the honorable Walter H. Annenberg, 1971 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A Proposal to W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1972 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A Proposal to Richard King Mellon Foundation, 1972 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- An Exploratory Proposal to Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1972 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A Proposal to Booth Ferris Foundation re: for partial support for a new Animal Care and Research Center, 1972 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A Proposal to the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation re: to support MD/PhD Biomedical Science Fellowships, 1973 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- A Proposal to the Kresge Foundation re: for the Construction of a New Animal Care and Research Center, 1973 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- An Exploratory Proposal to Josiah Macy Jr. Foundation re: for Support of MD/PhD Biomedical Science Program, 1973 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
- A Proposal to the Vincent Astor Foundation, 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 12)
- A Proposal to Charles Hayden Foundation re: for Construction of a New Animal Care and Research Center, 1973 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A Proposal Report to Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust re: Rockefeller University Field Research Center, 1973 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
- A Proposal to Max C. Fleischmann Foundation re: Summary of Program to Construct a New Animal Care and Research Center, 1973 December (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The Rockefeller University Council: Meeting, 1977 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Rockefeller University Council: Meeting, 1978 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- A Progress Report to the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation re: Research in Cell Biology at the Rockefeller University, 1979 February (Box 2, Folder 18)